api.ning.com 2010-05-27

# Ning - Legal: Privacy Policy Highlights

Effective: December 22, 2009

Your privacy is important to us. We want to make sure that you understand how information is collected, used, and disclosed on Ning.com and elsewhere on our social networking platform, so we created this notice to highlight some significant aspects of our full Ning Privacy Policy. For additional information regarding our privacy practices, please review our full Ning Privacy Policy. As always, if you have any questions about our privacy practices, we encourage you to contact us at [privacy@ning.com](mailto:privacy@ning.com).

Our Collection, Use, and Disclosure of Personal Information | Other Important Privacy Information  
---|---  
  
  * We collect personal information when you use our social networking platform or otherwise interact with us. This includes information you voluntarily provide, such as your name, email address, and date of birth, and some information that is collected automatically, such as information regarding your use of Ning Networks and applications on our social networking platform. 
  * We collect some information, including personal information, through the use of cookies, web beacons, and other technologies. 
  * We may also receive personal information from third-party sources, and may combine that information with other personal information we maintain. 
  * We may use personal information for various business purposes, such as to operate, provide, and maintain our services and systems; to develop new products and services; to personalize and display advertisements (via our own advertising engine or server) and other content; and to send you communications. 
  * We use industry standard security measures to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of personal information under our control. 
  * We do not rent or sell our members' personal information. Other than in the limited circumstances described in our full Privacy Policy, we do not disclose our members' personal information to third parties. 
  * We may provide personal information to third parties for their use in performing internal business functions on our behalf. We may also disclose personal information to third parties in some other limited circumstances, such as to protect our or third parties' rights, property, or safety. 
  * We also provide some personal information to Network Creators and developers of applications that operate on our platform. 

| 

  * The Children's Online Privacy Protection ACT (COPPA) protects the privacy of children under 13 years of age. In accordance with COPPA, we do not knowingly collect or maintain personal information from anyone under the age of 13. 
  * Network Creators using our platform, and developers of applications that run on our platform, also may collect and use personal information about you in accordance with their own privacy policies. 
  * We allow other companies to serve advertisements on our platform. These third-party companies may collect your IP address, other log file information, and other information about your activities on Ning. These third-party companies may use technologies such as cookies or web beacons to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize their advertising content. Certain of these third-party companies may also use these cookies to serve ads to you based on your activity on Ning Networks and on other sites on the Internet. Our full Privacy Policy provides information regarding opting-out from the collection of information by these third parties. 
  * We encourage you to review our full Privacy Policy for more detailed information about the ways in which we use, collect, and disclose personal information. 

Access and Choice | Updates and Contact Information  
  
  * You may at any time update, correct, or delete certain categories of personal information that you have provided to us by signing in to Ning and following the directions [here](http://help.ning.com/?faq=2820). 
  * You may update, correct, or delete certain categories of personal information within your profile pages on individual Ning Networks by following the directions [here](http://help.ning.com/?faq=3586). 
  * You have the ability to modify your privacy settings to limit the display of certain types of personal information displayed in your profiles on Ning Networks. 
  * You may terminate your Ning ID account at any time by following the directions [here](http://help.ning.com/?faq=2698) or contacting us using the contact information in this Privacy Highlights notice. 
  * When you are signed in to a Ning Network, you may indicate your preferences regarding certain administrative email messages by following the directions [here](http://help.ning.com/?faq=3415). 

| 

  * We may occasionally update our Privacy Policy. If we do, we will update the "effective date" at the top of the Privacy Policy. If we make an update to our Privacy Policy that is materially less restrictive in our use or disclosure of Personal Information that we collected prior to the update, we will provide you with prior notice of the pending update and seek your consent by posting notice on Ning.com or by contacting you using the email address that you have provided to us. 
  * If you have questions about our privacy practices, you may contact us at privacy@ning.com or by writing to us at:

 _Ning, Inc.  
285 Hamilton Street  
Suite 400  
Palo Alto, CA 94301  
Attn: Privacy Matters_
